A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1981; 0.56 Cubic Feet 42 microfilm reels (35mm); 42 Reels 42 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - United States, 1981; 1981/200
    - National (P-W), 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 268)
    - Na, 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 521)
    - New York Public Library (Card Catalog), 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 570)
    - New York University (E-W), 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 698)
    - New (E-Y), 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 812)
    - Ne, 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 943)
    - Northwestern University (K-U), 1981 (Reel 26, Frame 1008)
    - Ni-Nu, 1981 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - Oklahoma State University (E-F), 1981 (Reel 27, Frame 281)
    - O, 1981 (Reel 27, Frame 617)
    - Pa-Pe, 1981 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - Ph-Po, 1981 (Reel 28, Frame 232)
    - Princeton University (Rockefeller Public Service Award), 1981 (Reel 28, Frame 554)
    - Princeton University (B-U), 1981 (Reel 28, Frame 595)
    - Pr-Pu, 1981 (Reel 28, Frame 800)
    - Ra-Re, 1981 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - Rockefeller, 1981 (Reel 29, Frame 498)
    - Ri-Ru, 1981 (Reel 29, Frame 658)
    - Sarah Lawerence College (Ilchman, Alice), 1981 (Reel 29, Frame 1046)
    - Sa-Sc, 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Select Commission on Immigration and Refugee Policy, 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 245)
    - Se-Sh, 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 368)
    - Si-So, 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 544)
    - Standford University (F-S), 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 923)
    - State University of New York at Albany (H-S), 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - Stress and Families Initiatives Development Conference, 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 298)
    - Sp-Sy, 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 482)
    - Ta-Te, 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 731)
    - Th-To, 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 893)
    - Tr-Tw, 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agriculture (C-T), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 115)
    - United States (A-H), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 242)
    - United States (L-S), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 416)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights (Berry, Mary F), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 745)
    - United States Conference of Mayors (Mister, Melvin A.), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 774)
    - United States-Mexico Range Management Workshop, 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 794)
    - United Way of America, 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 906)
    - University (A), 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 945)
    - University of California (B-H), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - University of California (L-W), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 388)
    - University of Chicago (Schistosomiasis), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 660)
    - University of Chicago (S), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 961)
    - University (C-D), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 1046)
    - University of Florida (C-R), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 1065)
    - University of Florida (Veterinary Medicine), 1981 (Reel 33, Frame 1098)
    - University of Michigan (K-W), 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - University of Minnesota (B-W), 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 61)
    - University of Notre Dame (Urban Studies), 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 122)
    - University (H-N), 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 198)
    - University of Pennsylvania (Adolescent Pregnancy), 1981 (Reel 34, Frame 506)
    - University of Pennsylvania (D-W), 1981 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - University (P-R), 1981 (Reel 35, Frame 577)
    - University of Southern California (B-M), 1981 (Reel 35, Frame 639)
    - University of Wisconsin (D-Y), 1981 (Reel 35, Frame 848)
    - University (S-W), 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - U, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 89)
    - V, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 405)
    - Walker, Charls E., 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 470)
    - Washington University (Center for the Study of American Business), 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 562)
    - Wellesley College (K-M), 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 611)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art (Communications), 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 714)
    - W-Wh, 1981 (Reel 36, Frame 806)
    - Wi, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Wo, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 112)
    - Yale University(Parasitology Conference), 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 491)
    - Yale University (A-T), 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 595)
    - Y-Z, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 655)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1981; 1981/200.A
      Medical sciences
      - T-Y, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 758)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/200.E
      - M-W, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 836)
  - Philippines, 1981; 1981/242
    Philippines
    - A-T, 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 942)
    - University of the Philippines (A-D), 1981 (Reel 37, Frame 1088)
  - Fellowships in Higher Educational Administration (Minority), 1981; 1981/268
    - Chatman, Edna E., 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1981; 1981/272
    - B-N, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 10)
    - P-S, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 330)
  - South America, 1981; 1981/300
    South America
    - D-I, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 521)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1981; 1981/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 561)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/300.D
      Agriculture; Science
      - Central American Cooperative Program for Food Improvement, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 563)
  - Argentina, 1981; 1981/301
    Argentina
    - C-P, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 581)
  - Brazil, 1981; 1981/305
    Brazil
    - B-U, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 633)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/305.E
      - A-S, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 691)
  - Chile, 1981; 1981/309
    Chile
    - Catholic University (Cereals), 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 782)
    - C-L, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 850)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/309.D
      - Agriculture, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 871)
  - Colombia, 1981; 1981/311
    Colombia
    - B-R, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 876)
  - Honduras, 1981/321
    Honduras
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/321.D
      - Agriculture, 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 898)
  - Mexico, 1981; 1981/323
    Mexico
    - Agriculture (History), 1981 (Reel 38, Frame 1017)
    - A-U, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
  - Panama, 1981; 1981/327
    Panama
    - Gorgas Memorial Institute, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 145)
  - Peru, 1981; 1981/331
    Peru
    - G-R, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 147)
  - Dominican Republic, 1981; 1981/335
    Dominican Republic
    - Yunen, Rafael Emilio, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 153)
  - England, 1981; 1981/401
    England
    - Leakey, Colin L.A., 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 155)
    - B-M, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 292)
    - University of Sussex (H-R), 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 510)
    - N-W, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 554)
  - Ireland, 1981; 1981/403
    Ireland
    - C-R, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 753)
  - Australia, 1981; 1981/410
    Australia
    - A-U, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 802)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1981; 1981/420
    Caribbean Area; Central America
    - A-C, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 893)
  - Canada, 1981; 1981/427
    Canada
    - A-U, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 976)
  - Jamaica, 1981; 1981/437
    Jamaica
    - Fowler, Henry, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 1038)
  - Windward Islands, 1981; 1981/455
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Dominica, Grenada, St. Lucia, and St. Vincent.
    Windward Islands
    - Henry, Fitzroy J., 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 1041)
  - Hong Kong, 1981; 1981/463
    Hong Kong
    - Lisowski, F.P., 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 1044)
  - India, 1981; 1981/464
    India
    - D-V, 1981 (Reel 39, Frame 1046)
  - Pakistan, 1981; 1981/465
    Pakistan
    - Biggs, Tyler S., 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1981; 1981/466
    Bangladesh
    - C-R, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 10)
  - Malaysia, 1981; 1981/473
    Malaysia
    - J-S, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 54)
  - Nepal, 1981; 1981/474
    Nepal
    - G-N, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 102)
  - Africa, 1981; 1981/475
    Africa
    - Institute of Higher Learning in Africa, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 109)
  - Kenya, 1981; 1981/476
    Kenya
    - A-T, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 127)
    - University of Nairobi (G-S), 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 243)
  - East Africa Region, 1981; 1981/477
    Africa, East
    - I-Y, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 325)
  - Mauritius, 1981; 1981/478
    Mauritius
    - Rangasamy, Nethy, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 345)
  - South Africa Region, 1981; 1981/487
    Africa, Southern
    - Tusenius, Robert R., 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 358)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1981; 1981/489
    South Africa
    - Legal Resources Center, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 447)
  - Uganda, 1981; 1981/492
    Uganda
    - K-M, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 451)
    - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/492.D
      - Agriculture, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 481)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/492.E
      - Aniku, Jacob R.F., 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 562)
      - Baliddwa, Callistus W., 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 584)
      - Sabiiti, Elly N., 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 661)
  - Sudan, 1981; 1981/494
    Sudan
    - G-U, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 697)
  - West Africa, 1981; 1981/495
    Africa, West
    - Rice, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 707)
  - Ghana, 1981; 1981/496
    Ghana
    - G-U, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 895)
  - Nigeria, 1981; 1981/497
    Nigeria
    - A-P, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 901)
  - Sierra Leone, 1981; 1981/499
    Sierra Leone
    - Lahai, Aloysius Cyril, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 910)
  - France, 1981; 1981/500
    France
    - C-V, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 915)
  - Senegal, 1981; 1981/531
    Senegal
    - A-D, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 996)
  - China, 1981; 1981/601
    China
    - Liu, Chi-Wu, 1981 (Reel 40, Frame 1024)
    - C-Z, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - China - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/601.E
      - Cheng, Wei-Zhong, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 36)
  - Taiwan, 1981; 1981/605
    Taiwan
    - A-S, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 49)
  - Japan, 1981; 1981/609
    Japan
    - J, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 60)
  - Thailand, 1981; 1981/617
    Thailand
    - Chulalongkorn University (C-S), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 74)
    - N-T, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 129)
    - University of Thammasat (E-P), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 137)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/617.E
      - Chatima Ongsuragz, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 266)
  - Holland, 1981; 1981/650
    Netherlands
    - E-M, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 269)
  - Indonesia, 1981; 1981/652
    Indonesia
    - Gadjah Mada University (C-S), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 433)
    - A-G, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 496)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/652.E
      - Sumarjuno, Maria Sri Wulani, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 502)
  - Ethiopia, 1981; 1981/701
    Ethiopia
    - Courtejoie, J., 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 514)
  - Austria, 1981; 1981/705
    Austria
    - Austrian College Society (Alpach European Forum), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 526)
  - Belgium, 1981; 1981/707
    Belgium
    - Baudoin, J.P., 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 555)
  - Belgian Congo, 1981; 1981/709
    Congo (Democratic Republic)
    - C-N, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 598)
    - Belgian Congo - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/709.E
      - Nwema, Ntambu, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 610)
  - Germany, 1981; 1981/717
    Germany
    - B-T, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 651)
  - Tanganyika, 1981; 1981/723
    Tanzania
    - K-U, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 849)
  - Togo, 1981; 1981/745
    Togo
    - Karbe, Eberhard, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 868)
  - Greece, 1981; 1981/749
    Greece
    - Vithoulkas, George, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 871)
  - Italy, 1981; 1981/751
    Italy
    - A-V, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 874)
  - Norway, 1981; 1981/767
    Norway
    - Christian Michelsen Institute (Faaland, Just), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 935)
  - Iran, 1981; 1981/771
    Iran
    - Sepasy, Bijan, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 947)
  - Portugal, 1981; 1981/773
    Portugal
    - A-S, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 952)
  - Poland, 1981; 1981/789
    Poland
    - Pieniazek, Szczepan A., 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 982)
  - Sweden, 1981; 1981/800
    Sweden
    - University of Stockholm (Boman, Hans G.), 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 1002)
  - Switzerland, 1981; 1981/803
    Switzerland
    - D-H, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 1067)
  - Turkey, 1981; 1981/805
    Turkey
    - C-M, 1981 (Reel 41, Frame 1083)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/805.D
      - Agriculture, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
  - Egypt, 1981; 1981/812
    Egypt
    - A-Y, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 14)
    - Egypt - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1981; 1981/812.D
      - Agriculture, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 56)
  - Israel, 1981; 1981/825
    Israel
    - Hebrew University (Patinkin, Don), 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 123)
    - C-Y, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 127)
  - Lebanon, 1981; 1981/833
    Lebanon
    - A-I, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 290)
  - Members and Meetings, 1981; 1981/903
    - B-W, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 453)
  - Humanities, 1981/911
    Humanities
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/911.E
      - Engs, Robert, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 661)
      - B-L, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 727)
      - M-S, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 857)
      - T-W, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 1090)
  - Art History, 1981/925
    - Art History - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/925.E
      - Lucier, Mary, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 1208)
  - Environmental Affairs, 1981/927
    - Environmental Affairs - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/927.E
      - Harkonen, W. Scott, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 1234)
  - Geographic Medicine, 1981/928
    - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, 1981; 1981/928.E
      - C-S, 1981 (Reel 42, Frame 1238)
- General Correspondence, 1982; 0.52 Cubic Feet 39 microfilm reels (35mm); 39 Reels 39 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1982; 1982/100
    - Abin, Leonardo, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Anderson, Bernard E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 12)
    - Arbab, Farzam, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 16)
    - Arthurs, Alberta, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 50)
    - Bonman, Michael, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 60)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 77)
    - Bowers, John Z., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 118)
    - Bruer, John Thomas, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 123)
    - Buchwalter, Ellen Shapiro, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 127)
    - Cahn, Steven M., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 129)
    - Campbell, Donald R., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 131)
    - Colten, Joel, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 157)
    - Cottingham, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 165)
    - Court, David, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 167)
    - Crowder, Loy V., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 169)
    - Dapice, David O., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 292)
    - Davidson, Ralph K., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 298)
    - Deagle, Edwin A., Jr., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 302)
    - Delehanty, George E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 306)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 310)
    - Eckholm, Erik P., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 357)
    - Elliott, Howard, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 374)
    - Garrity, Dennis P., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 377)
    - Goffman, William, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 384)
    - Gossage, Wayne, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 388)
    - Grant, Ulysses J., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 390)
    - Gray, Clarence C., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 404)
    - Greenburg, Bernard G., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 407)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 412)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 437)
    - Hopkins, Kevin D., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 446)
    - House, Leland R., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 454)
    - Howe, Charles W., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 465)
    - Huddleston, Barbara, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 467)
    - Jackson, Ben R., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 564)
    - Jennings, Peter R., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 582)
    - Johnson, Loyd, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 598)
    - Johnston, James E., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 659)
    - Katz, Stephen M., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 661)
    - Klein, Pat, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 664)
    - Laird, Reggie J., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 666)
    - Lark, Karl G., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 706)
    - Lavine, Steven David, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 713)
    - Lyle, Katherine Ch'iu, 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 717)
    - Lyman, Judith M., 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 720)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Council for Financial Aid to Education), 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 745)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Jefferson Medal), 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 798)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Recommendations)Lyman, Richard W. (Recommendations), 1982 (Reel 1, Frame 837)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (Speeches), 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (January-March), 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 69)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (April-June), 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 164)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (July-August), 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 428)
    - Lyman, Richard W. (September-December), 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 474)
    - Maner, Jerome H., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 500)
    - Mann, Charles K., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 507)
    - Martinez S., Eugenio, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 539)
    - Martinez Gutierrez, Mario A., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 548)
    - McCarthy, Kathleen D., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 568)
    - McIntyre, Ian, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 571)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 598)
    - McLean, Sheila Avrin, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 605)
    - Meyer, Jack R., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 658)
    - Mock, Christopher Alden, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 661)
    - Moock, Joyce L., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 676)
    - Mullen, Lynda, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 678)
    - Myers, Rosemary E., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 680)
    - Oshima, Harry T., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 689)
    - Osler, Robert D., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 712)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 716)
    - Pino, John A., 1982 (Reel 2, Frame 718)
    - Posner, Joshua L., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 185)
    - Rajic, Vera, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 231)
    - Ramanathan, Rajaram, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 233)
    - Renfro, Bobby L., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 235)
    - Rensberger, Judith, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 349)
    - Sar, Marcin, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 354)
    - Sechler, Susan, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 358)
    - Segal, Sheldon, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 363)
    - Smeltzer, Dale G., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 370)
    - Smith, Herbert L., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 378)
    - Spain, Jim, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 380)
    - Sprague, Ernest W., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 383)
    - Stewart, Michael M., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 387)
    - Stifel, Laurence D., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 391)
    - Stremlau, John J., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 394)
    - Suchart, Upatham, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 396)
    - Szwaja, Lynn Alison, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 401)
    - Theberge, Robert L., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 403)
    - Toenniessen, Gary H., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 443)
    - Walsh, Julia A., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 460)
    - Warren, Kenneth S., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 465)
    - Warwick, Esther J., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 615)
    - Watawabe, Wade, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 623)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 625)
    - White, Kerr L., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 687)
    - Williams, B.E., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 692)
    - Woolf, Patricia, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 694)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling, 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 706)
    - Wright, Bill C., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 708)
    - Young, William R., 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 719)
  - International Organizations, 1982; 1982/103
    - Institute for World Order (Reardon, Betty), 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 791)
    - Institute (C-W), 1982 (Reel 3, Frame 972)
    - International Bank (A-Y), 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - International (A-C), 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 80)
    - International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study, 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 532)
    - International (F-V), 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 641)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (B-N), 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 728)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (B-P), 1982 (Reel 4, Frame 832)
    - United Nations (E-T), 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Development Programme (C-N), 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 106)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (de Weck, J. B.), 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 150)
    - United Nations Institute for DIsarmament Research (Bota, Liviu), 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 164)
    - United Nations University (S-W), 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 203)
    - D-E, 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 299)
    - I-P, 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 302)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1982; 1982/120
    - B-L, 1982 (Reel 5, Frame 713)
    - O-W, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
  - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations, 1982; 1982/155
    - B-S, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 282)
  - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research, 1982/175
    - Equal Opportunity - Basic Rights/Policy Research - Fellowships, 1982; 1982/175.E
      - D-G, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 438)
  - Special Interests and Explorations - Immigrants, 1982; 1982/181
    - A-W, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 516)
  - Conquest of Hunger - Marginal Lands and Fragile Environments, 1982; 1982/190
    - Hillside Agriculture Conference, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 687)
  - United States, 1982; 1982/200
    - Ac-Af, 1982 (Reel 6, Frame 781)
    - Ag-Al, 1982 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - American (A-C), 1982 (Reel 7, Frame 371)
    - American (D-F), 1982 (Reel 7, Frame 744)
    - American (H-P), 1982 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - American (R-T), 1982 (Reel 8, Frame 391)
    - Am - Ar, 1982 (Reel 8, Frame 500)
    - Association of American Colleges (Undergraduate Curriculum Conference), 1982 (Reel 8, Frame 734)
    - As- Au, 1982 (Reel 8, Frame 856)
    - Bates, Robert H., 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Ba, 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 174)
    - Be, 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 685)
    - Boston University (G-M), 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 804)
    - Bl - Bo, 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 842)
    - Brandeis University (E-S), 1982 (Reel 9, Frame 947)
    - Br-Bu, 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Carnegie Foundation (January-April), 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 233)
    - Carnegie Foundation (June), 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 537)
    - Carnegie Foundation (September-October), 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 708)
    - Ca, 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 829)
    - Center (A-I), 1982 (Reel 10, Frame 961)
    - Center (L-R), 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Central (I-N), 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 193)
    - Charles County Community College (Sine, John M.), 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 212)
    - Chatham College, 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 231)
    - Chicago State University, 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 259)
    - Christie, John D., 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 272)
    - Ch, 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 303)
    - City University of New York (M-U), 1982 (Reel 11, Frame 902)
    - Ci, 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Clark Foundation (Harlow, Hattie Dorsey), 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 79)
    - Cl, 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 226)
    - Columbia University (A-W), 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 407)
    - Cornell University (H-W), 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 457)
    - Council (A-L), 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 565)
    - Co, 1982 (Reel 12, Frame 762)
    - Cr-Cu, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Dartmouth College (H-R), 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 29)
    - D-Di, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 51)
    - Duke University (I-V), 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 171)
    - Do-Du, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 337)
    - Ea-Ei, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 677)
    - En-Er, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 915)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 978)
    - Fa-Fe, 1982 (Reel 13, Frame 1030)
    - Florida (I-S), 1982 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Ford Foundation (B-T), 1982 (Reel 14, Frame 183)
    - Fi-Fo, 1982 (Reel 14, Frame 526)
    - Fr-Fu, 1982 (Reel 14, Frame 869)
    - Ga-Gl, 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Gn-Gu, 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 229)
    - Harvard University (G-S), 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 490)
    - Hawaii (Native Hawaiian Development Office), 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 709)
    - Ha, 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 794)
    - He-Hi, 1982 (Reel 15, Frame 985)
    - Howard University (Burnette, Alice G.), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ho - Hu, 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 42)
    - Illinois Benedictine College (Block, Walter), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 170)
    - Indiana University (Byrnes, Robert F.), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 276)
    - Institute (A-W), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 295)
    - Inter-American University Council, 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 530)
    - International (B-V), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 819)
    - Iowa State University (S-T), 1982 (Reel 16, Frame 1017)
    - I, 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Johns Hopkins University (A-U), 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 268)
    - J, 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 405)
    - K, 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 552)
    - La, 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 889)
    - League of Women Education Fund (B-H), 1982 (Reel 17, Frame 931)
    - Le - Li, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 257)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (Supplementary Material), 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 435)
    - Lo - Ly, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 550)
    - Ma, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 626)
    - Mc, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 854)
    - Me, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 908)
    - Michigan State University (Hamilton, Ruth S.), 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 998)